## **DEISE KOREEDA**

New York, NY +1 215-600-8462 deise.koreeda@gmail.com Linkedin Github

#### **PROFILE**

As an engineer and a web developer, I am able to merge engineering with coding to develop efficient and creative web solutions. My previous work experience in the business side of healthcare enables me to acknowledge business core values and prioritize tasks to manage costs as well as to leverage a company's profitability.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5 Cascading Style Sheets JavaScript jQuery Node.js Express.js PostgreSQL Photoshop
InDesign Microsoft Office Illustrator Team Leadership Project Management AJAX

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## GENERAL ASSEMBLY Web Development Immersive Program

New York, USA 2017-2017

- Project 1: Connect 4 A two players game, which the goal is to get four pieces of the same color connected in a row, vertically or diagonally. Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, and Javascript. (<a href="https://github.com/dkoreeda/connect4">https://github.com/dkoreeda/connect4</a>)
- Project 2: Travel Planner A web application developed to help travelers to create their own itinerary or save wishlist with places of a specific city. Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, jQuery, Node.js, Google Maps API, PostgreSQL. (MVC structure <a href="https://github.com/dkoreeda/unconventional-trip">https://github.com/dkoreeda/unconventional-trip</a>)
- Project 3: Attender A web application developed to help teachers to take students attendance in class. Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, jQuery, Ruby on Rails, Google Maps API, and PostgreSQL. (MVC structure <a href="https://attender.herokuapp.com/">https://attender.herokuapp.com/</a>)

# AIR LIQUIDE - VITALAIRE National Operations Analyst

São Paulo, Brazil 2013-2015

- Mapped and identified improvement opportunities in operational processes including inventory management, transportation and distribution, customer service and maintenance
- Led planning and implementation of new in-house system for customer service, including call center and CRM
- Managed annual budget of medical equipment inventory, involving purchase, turnover and obsolescence of inventory items
- Monitored annual budget of operating costs, identifying and addressing opportunities for cost savings

#### **VOLUNTEERING**

## CHILDREN'S HOME ORPHANAGE English Tutor

Prague, Czech Republic 2013

- Lectured English for 40 children aged 9-18, prepared and delivered lectures, provided homework tutoring and developed learning games
- Mentored orphan teenagers in general life issues, such as relationship, health, education and career

#### **EDUCATION**

#### UNIVERSIDADE FEDERAL DO ABC

Bachelor of Biomedical Engineering

Sao Paulo, Brazil 2009-2013

• Developed research project for the Hospital of the University of Campinas to assess operational costs of breast cancer diagnosis and identify improvement opportunities

## UNIVERSIDADE FEDERAL DO ABC

Bachelor of Science and Technology

Sao Paulo, Brazil 2005-2007

- Developed research project for improvement of techniques for contaminant degradation using visible light and photo catalyst components, presented results in Congress of Brazilian Chemical Society
- President of Women's Soccer Club